# **Duncan Kinungi**

+254704 583 451 • 22713-00400, Nairobi Kenya • kinungiduncan@gmail.com

## **ICT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN**

## Allocation & Maintenance of IT Equipment | Diagnose Hardware and Software Issues | Review and Resolve IT Help-desk Requests

Motivated IT support technician who seeks a new position in dynamic, growth-oriented company focused on cultivating exceptional customer experience and a positive work environment. With experience handling networking concerns, implementing new software, installing new hardware, and addressing user concerns, I bring attention to detail and a dedication to technical improvement to each job. Past achievements include new network architecture component selection and implementation, earning leading industry certifications, and driving the achievement of departmental goals.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Dundeonx Technologies**

## **Front-end Developer**

03/2021- Present

With a strong foundation in computer skills, I'm passionate about web design and development, and interested in mobile app development. As I grow as a developer, I hope to write clean, readable code that can be used by others and leveraged to create beautiful software.

## Silver-Dean Co LTD

#### Call Center Agent

01/2021- 03/2021

Building a positive attitude towards customers by satisfying their day today queries.

- Actively working as an Inbound Team.
- Conversant with Ameyo Call Agent App in terms of call Disposition coding.
- Raising Tickets on Atlas and Updating Call Notes.
- Escalating Tickets on Jira.

## **Quick Call Solutions LTD**

#### **Team Lead Sales Executive on Safaricom Products.**

06/2019-12/2020

Developed and improved the capabilities of sales representative team over the course of one year.

- Received 97% satisfaction rating from customers after completed phone or video call.
- Kept records of customer interactions, processed customer accounts and filed documents.
- Collaborated with team to quickly resolve customer complaints with appropriate action.
- Effectively managed approximately 100 incoming calls daily.

## +254704583451 01/2019 - 05/2019

#### BEST WESTERN PLUS MERIDIAN HOTEL

#### **ICT Support Technician**

Used strong communication skills to collaborate with team members to ensure efficient service.

- Firewall configuration and usage (Sophos and zentyal).
- Installing software's.
- Safes and onity door locks.
- Coordinated the repair and maintenance of office supplies and equipment bi-weekly.

#### UNITED STATES UNIVERSITY – AFRICA

08/2017 - 12/2017

## **ICT Support Technician**

- Troubleshooting system and Network problems and solving hardware/software faults.
- Installation, administration and troubleshooting of various Linux PCs'.
- Setting up new users' accounts and profiles & dealing with password issues.
- Setting up and troubleshooting of multimedia equipment such as projectors, computer system for power point presentations.
- Maintaining the multimedia Bookings calendar up to date.
- Receiving and redirecting calls.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **INSTITUTE OF SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGIES**

Diploma in Information Security - November 2018

#### INSTITUTE OF ADVANCED TECHNOLOGY

Diploma in information communication Technology Management - December 2017

## KING SEJONG INSTITUTE

Certificate in Korean Language and Literature - November 2015

## NAIROBI AVIATION COLLEGE

Diploma in Business Information Systems - December 2015

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Mastery of Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint) and Google Suite (Docs, Sheets, Slides).
- Comfortable working in both Microsoft Windows 10, Mac OS X and Linux.
- Excellent communication skills with a focus on team-building.
- Outstanding organizational, multitasking, and problem-solving abilities.

## **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

#### MASABA SERVICES

02/2018-04/2018

## **Duties and responsibilities:**

- Installing, supporting and configuring of WiMAX.
- Pulling cable, Splicing and fiber installation.
- Router configuration and LAN set up.

Duncan Kinungi +254704583451

• Survey of all technologies; Wi-Fi, Microwave, E1.

## **PARTICIPATIONS**

## **Linux Administration**

Living Open Source an ITGilde initiative (Linux) Hosted at University of Nairobi

## **REFERENCES**

Name: Erickson Kimiti Kibui

Job Title: ICT Officer United States University -Africa

Email: kibserikson@gmail.com

**Tel:** +254-721-364-251

Name: Samuel Kuiyoni

Job Title: ICT Manager Best Western Plus Meridian Hotel

Email: samuelkuiyoni@gmail.com

**Tel:** +254-708-919-151